Register of the Center for the Study of Popular Culture Records
Hoover Institution Archives
Center for the Study of Popular Culture Records
1988-2003.
2005C25
Center for the Study of Popular Culture.
Horowitz, David, 1939-
124 manuscript boxes. (74 linear feet)
Hoover Institution on War, Revolution, and Peace Stanford, California 94305-6010
Writings, correspondence, memoranda, schedules, legal and financial records, printed matter, sound recordings, and video tape, relating to conservatism and the mass media in the United States. Includes papers of David Horowitz, founder and president of the Center.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research. Access to audiovisual materials requires at least two weeks advance notice. Audiovisual materials include sound recordings, video recordings, and motion picture film. Hoover staff will determine whether use copies of the materials requested can be made available. Some materials may not be accessible even with advance notice. Please contact the Hoover Institution Archives Audiovisual Specialist for further information.
Acquisition Information
The collection was acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2005.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog Socrates at http://library.stanford.edu/webcat. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in Socrates is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Historical Note
The Center for the Study of Popular Culture, based in Los Angeles, California, was founded in 1988 by David Horowitz, president of the Center since the beginning, and Peter Collier, his associate.
The Center's objectives are to promote traditional conservative values, especially regarding racial and social issues, and mold public opinion by challenging opposing points of view. To achieve these goals the Center distributes pamphlets, links its website to others with similar goals, probes political affiliations of members of academic institutions, and campaigns in favor of anti-liberal talk shows and other programs. The Center has worked with an organization of conservative college students and the Committee for Media Integrity (COMINT) to focus public attention on the liberal bias it sees in the media. In addition, David Horowitz personally contributes to the mission of the Center by promoting his books, appearing on radio and television programs, and speaking on college campuses around the country.
The Center has three branches: FrontPage Magazine, a daily online journal; Wednesday Morning Club, a forum to promote conservative ideas in the media and entertainment industries; and the Individual Rights Foundation, which provides legal support to the Center and litigates constitutional rights cases.
Contributions from private organizations with conservative affiliations, such as the Bradley Foundation, Carthage Foundation, Olin Foundation, Richard Scaife Foundation, and others, have enabled the Center to build a strong financial base.
Scope and Content of Collection
Acquired in 2003, the Center for the Study of Popular Culture records consist of writings, correspondence, memoranda, schedules, legal and financial records, printed matter, sound recordings, and videorecordings, relating to conservatism and the mass media in the United States. The collection includes papers of David Horowitz, founder and president of the Center.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Subjects
United States--Politics and government--1989-; Conservatism.; Mass media--United States.; Horowitz, David,--1939-
Genre
Phonotapes; Video tapes.
Container List
- Johnson Foundation, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 1: 1)
- Koret Foundation, 2000-2001 (Folder 1: 2)
- John M. Olin Foundation, 1980-1999 (Folder 1: 3-13)
- Nations Bank Corporation, 1995 (Folder 1: 14)
- Noble Foundation, 1996 (Folder 1: 15)
- Normark Associates, 1996 (Folder 1: 16)
- Life Enrichment Foundation, 2000 (Folder 1: 17)
- Amy Shelton McNutt Trust, 1995 (Folder 1: 18)
- Merrill Lynch and Company Foundation, Inc., undated and 1996 (Folder 1: 19)
- Frank S. Meyer Society, 1992 (Folder 1: 20)
- Milken Families Foundation, 1995-1996 (Folder 1: 21)
- Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing Company, undated (Folder 1: 22)
- Mobil Foundation, Inc., 1996 (Folder 1: 23)
- J. P. Morgan and Company, 1996-2000 (Folder 1: 24)
- Motorola, undated (Folder 1: 25)
- Charles Stewart Mott Foundation, 1995 (Folder 1: 26)
- M. J. Murdock Charitable Trust, 1993-1996 (Folder 1: 27)
- McClellan Foundation, 1993-1995 (Folder 1: 28)
- Martin Marietta Corporation, undated (Folder 1: 29)
- Cordelia S. May Family Trust, 1994-1997 (Folder 1: 30-32)
- Neil A. McConnell Foundation, Inc., 1995 (Folder 1: 33)
- MCA Foundation, 1995 (Folder 1: 34)
- McCune Foundation, 1993-1998 (Folder 1: 35-36)
- Katherine Mabis McKenna Foundation, 1995 (Folder 1: 37)
- International Foundation for Personal Freedom, 1995 (Folder 1: 38)
- Eli Lilly and Company, undated and 1996 (Folder 1: 39)
- Lilly Endowment, 1993-1996 (Folder 1: 40)
- Loews Corporation, 1996 (Folder 1: 41)
- Lowe's Companies, undated and 1996 (Folder 1: 42)
- Henry Luce Foundation, 1993 (Folder 1: 43)
- Lyndhurst Foundation, 1993 (Folder 1: 44)
- J. M. Foundation, 1989-1999 (Folder 1: 45)
- W. K. Kellogg Foundation, 1995 (Folder 1: 46)
- Peter Kewitt Foundation, 1995 (Box-folder 2: 1)
- Kiplinger Foundation, 1995 (Folder 2: 2)
- John S. and James L. Knight Foundation, 1995 (Folder 2: 3)
- Charles G. Koch Foundation, Inc., 1994-1998 (Folder 2: 4-7)
- Eastman Kodak Company, 1991 (Folder 2: 8)
- Kohler Charitable Fund, 1999 (Folder 2: 9)
- Kraft General Foods, 1994 (Folder 2: 10)
- Koret Foundation, 1996-1999 (Folder 2: 11-13)
- Vernon K. Krieble Foundation, 1998-1999 (Folder 2: 14)
- Kovner Foundation, 1999 (Folder 2: 15)
- Helen Krieble Foundation, 1997-1999 (Folder 2: 16)
- Claude R. Lambe Charitable Fund, 1997 (Folder 2: 17)
- Laurel Foundation, 1996 (Folder 2: 18)
- Life Enrichment Foundation, 1997 (Folder 2: 19)
- Philip Morris Companies, 1989; 1993-2000 (Folder 2: 20-21)
- Montgomery Street Foundation, 1993 and; 1999-2000 (Folder 2: 22-23)
- Philip M. McKenna Foundation, Inc., 1993-1995 (Folder 2: 24)
- M. J. Murdock Charitable Trust, 1991-1993 (Folder 2: 25)
- Randolph Foundation, 1992-1995 (Folder 2: 26-29)
- PacifiCare, 1996 (Folder 2: 30)
- Pepsico Foundation, 1996 (Folder 2: 31)
- Pew Charitable Trust, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 3: 1-2)
- Pfizer, 1995 (Folder 3: 3)
- Phillips Petroleum Foundation, 1992-1996 (Folder 3: 4)
- Pennsylvania Manufacturers Association Foundation, 1997-1998 (Folder 3: 5)
- John William Pope Foundation, 1993-1999 (Folder 3: 6)
- 50 compact sound cassettes, 1991-2002 (Box 4)
- 11 DVDs and 34 mini sound cassettes, undated (Box 5)
- 30 compact sound cassettes, undated and 1992-2001 (Box 6)
- Report Cards, 1995-1997 (Box 7)
- The Defender, 1994
- The Defender, 1994-1997 (Box 8)
- Center News, 1994-1998
- 67 VHS videocassettes, undated and 1990-2000 (Box 9-14)
- Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 15: 1)
- Capital donor research, 1997-1998. (Folder 15: 2)
  Clippings and printed matter
- Kick Drugs out of America Foundation, 1998. (Folder 15: 3)
  Brochure, notes, and report
- Street dreams, undated. (Folder 15: 4)
  Notes
- City Hearts, 1998-1999. (Folder 15: 5)
  Correspondence, memoranda, notes, and miscellany
- Americans for School Choice, 1993. (Folder 15: 6)
  Brochure and press release
- Center for Individual Rights, 1994-1995. (Folder 15: 7)
  Report of activities
- Preference Communications, 1997. (Folder 15: 8)
  Letter to Eve Burud from Christiane Carlson-Thies
- Operation Hope--John Bryant, 1998. (Folder 15: 9)
  Program, fliers, notes, printed matter, and report
- Retirement savings plan enrollment kit--Fidelity Investments, undated (Folder 15: 10)
- Minutes of the board meeting, 1996. (Folder 15: 11)
  Includes printed matter
- Nicholls Consulting, 1995-1998. (Folder 15: 12)
  Invoices, letters, and notes
- United States Postal Service, 1998. (Folder 15: 13)
  Letter
- Computer cable rewiring, 1997 (Folder 15: 14)
- Bio coastal Communications, 1996-1998. (Folder 15: 15)
  Miscellany
- Phone system, 1998 (Folder 15: 16)
- IRF budgets/projects, 1997. (Folder 15: 17)
  Expense records, memoranda, and miscellany
- Credit line, 1997. (Folder 15: 18)
- Economic census, 1997. (Folder 15: 19)
  Form and related materials
- Budget/aging report, 1997 (Folder 15: 20)
- Annual report, 1996 (Folder 15: 21)
- Budget, 1998. (Folder 15: 22)
  Memoranda, salary and befits records, profit and loss statement, and related materials
- Lincoln Club, undated.
  List of names
- Attendance record, 1995
- Correspondence and memoranda, 1997
- Printed matter, 1991-1992
- Membership programs and related information, 1997 (Box-folder 16: 1)
- Foundation activity, 1994-1997. (Folder 16: 2)
  List of grants, profit and loss statements, and miscellany
- Corporate and Foundation giving records, 1997. (Folder 16: 3)
  List of donors and amount of donations
- Planned giving, 1997. (Folder 16: 4)
  Brochure, letter, and miscellany
- African Community Resource Center, 1998. (Folder 16: 5)
  Agenda for the project, background information, clipping, draft invitations, letter, and list of committee members
- Chevron/Shannon Reeves, 1998. (Folder 16: 6)
  Brochure, clipping, letter, and press release
- Best Friends event, 1997. (Folder 16: 7-8)
  Clippings, fact sheet about Best Friends Foundation, journal, list of conservative members of the House of Representatives, newsletter, and miscellany
- Ambassador Glen Holden, 1998. (Folder 16: 9)
  Information kit
- Walt Disney Co., 1997. (Folder 16: 10)
  Clippings, financial records, letters, memoranda, newsletter, and miscellany
- Individual Rights Foundation, 1994-2000. (Folder 16: 11)
  Article, book, brochure, magazine, and 1 compact disc
- Center's funding report, 1997
- 1960s--Clippings, 1991 (Box-folder 17: 1)
- Correspondence with (Folder 17: 2)
  - Varied Directions, Inc., 1990
  - Jim Exxon, 1991
  - Jennifer Lawson, 1991
- Miscellany, 1989-1991.
  Includes brochures, clippings, correspondence, journals, notes, remarks, and reports
- Clippings, 1987-2002. (Box-folder 18: 1-5)
  Includes "Ten Reasons Why Reparations for Slavery Is a Bad Idea and Racist Too," by David Horowitz and issues of The Purdue Independent and Counterpoint
- College newspapers, 1992-2002 (Box-folder 19: 1-2)
- Palmer R. Chitester Fund, 1980-1991 (Folder 19: 3)
- Letters to David Horowitz, 1987-1991 (Folder 19: 4)
- David Horowitz--Sketches, undated (Folder 19: 5)
- Environment, 1991. (Folder 19: 6)
  Clipping
- Korea, 1990. (Folder 19: 7)
  Clippings and newsletters
- Philanthropy, 2003 (Folder 19: 8)
- The Kennedys: An American Drama by David Horowitz and Peter Collier--Publication contract, 1986 January 20 (Folder 19: 9)
- Letters from Jim Exxon and Alvin Perlmutter and letter to Ted Stevens, 1991. (Folder 19: 10)
  Includes related clippings and printed matter
- Correspondence relating to the program, "Fire from the Sun,", 1990. (Folder 19: 11)
  Includes clipping, 1991
- COMINT, 1991. (Folder 19: 12-13)
  Includes correspondence, clippings, and miscellany
- Bill Moyers, 1991. (Folder 19: 14)
  Clippings and printed matter. Includes a letter to the editor
- Interview of David Horowitz by Rona Mendelsohn, 1980 (Folder 19: 15)
- KBOO FM Program Guide, 1992 (Folder 19: 16)
- Vanguard--Portland State University, 1992 (Folder 19: 17)
- Advertisements in newspapers, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 20: 1)
- Miscellany, 1977; 1984-1987,; 1991-1996,; and 2003 (Folder 20: 2)
- Vietnam Memorial, 1992 (Folder 20: 3)
- "PC Riot,", undated. (Folder 20: 4)
  Revisions
- 128 VHS videocassettes relating to political, social, and religious issues, 1991-1999 (Box 21-31)
- 37 compact sound cassettes, 1989-2002. (Box 32)
  Includes series, "The 1st 100 Days with David Horowitz," and "Second Thoughts;" remarks and interviews about education, conservative values, and political issues
- 35 compact sound cassettes, 1992-1997. (Box 33)
  Contains mostly "1st 100 Days with David Horowitz" and "Second Thoughts" programs
- 38 compact sound cassettes, 1992-1995. (Box 34)
  "The 1st 100 Days with David Horowitz" and "Second Thoughts" programs
- 39 compact sound cassettes, 1992-2000. (Box 35)
  "The 1st 100 Days with David Horowitz" and "Second Thoughts" programs. Includes conversations with politicians and journalists, such as Dick Armey, Fred Barnes, Tom Delay, William Kristol, and Chris Mathews
- 36 compact sound cassettes, 1992-1994. (Box 36)
  Contains mostly "Second Thoughts" programs
- 37 compact sound cassettes, 1992-1995 (Box 37)
  --"1st 100 Days with David Horowitz" programs. Includes dialogues with John McCain
- 30 compact sound cassettes, 1992-1994. (Box 38)
  Mostly "Second Thoughts" programs
- 3 compact sound cassettes, undated.
  Publicly produced programs containing interview and discussion of political issues by private individuals and journalists
- 35 compact sound cassettes, 1992-1994. (Box 39)
  Mostly "Second Thoughts" programs dealing with political and religious issues
- 49 compact sound cassettes, 1994-1995. (Box 40)
  Mostly "1st 100 Days with David Horowitz". Also includes speeches by David Horowitz relating to social issues; political agenda of the Republican Party; and media politics
- Golf accommodations, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 41: 1)
- President's Golf Challenge: Golfing for Kids--Volunteer/staff information, 1996 (Folder 41: 2)
- Golf
  - Letterhead, undated (Folder 41: 3)
  - Bob Levy correspondence, 1995-1996 (Folder 41: 4)
- Omaha Sunday World Herald, Omaha, Nebraska, 1995 January 15. (Folder 41: 5)
  Includes miscellaneous materials
- Auction items, 1996. (Folder 41: 6)
  Letters, notes, and miscellany
- Miscellany, 1996. (Folder 41: 7)
  Includes materials relating to the Golfing for Kids program
- Marketing Golf Resource Corporation--Background information, 1996 May 29.
  Includes a letter to Kevin Teasley and Stacy Katz, memorandum, and a proposal
- Rancho Valencia Resort--Information, 1996
- Independent Events and Media and Wheel Friends of Childhelp, 1995-1996.
  List and memoranda
- Golfing for Kids (Box 42)
  - Finances/invoices, 1996 (Folder 42: 1)
  - Graphics, 1996 (Folder 42: 2)
  - Program booklet, 1996 (Folder 42: 3)
  - Media-public relations, 1996 (Folder 42: 4)
  - La Costa event--Banquet planning, 1996 (Folder 42: 5)
  - Golfing original documents, 1996 (Folder 42: 6)
  - Golf invitees, 1996 (Folder 42: 7)
  - Fliers and miscellany, 1996 (Folder 42: 8-9)
  - Golf event, 1996 (Box-folder 43: 1-2)
  - Golfers information, 1996 (Folder 43: 3)
  - Denied sponsorship, 1996 (Folder 43: 4)
  - Golf corporate sponsors, 1996 (Folder 43: 5)
  - Golf sponsors (copies), 1996 (Folder 43: 6)
  - Golf follow up/thank you letters, 1996 (Folder 43: 7)
  - Confirmed contest prizes/sponsorship, 1996 (Folder 43: 8)
- Orange County Republican Women's Federation--Brunch and general meeting, 1998 April 18. (Box-folder 44: 1)
  Invitation and miscellany
- Remarks, Republican National Committee Eagles summer national meeting, San Francisco, California, 1998 June 26-27. (Folder 44: 2)
  Itinerary and miscellany
- National Republican Senatorial Committee--Invitation to participate in a panel discussion, Los Angeles, California, 1998 July 10-11 (Folder 44: 3)
- Jonathan Breakfast Club, Los Angeles, California, 1998 July 21. (Folder 44: 4)
  Invitation to speak and related materials
- Invitation to speak, Lincoln wine-tasting reception, California, 1998 July 21. (Folder 44: 5)
- Speaking engagement in support of Rick Jackson, Seattle, Washington, 1998 July 25. (Folder 44: 6)
  Letters by David Horowitz and receipt
- Fundraising event, San Francisco, California, 1998 August 19-21 (Folder 44: 7)
- The John Locke Foundation, Raleigh, North Carolina, 1998 September 2. (Folder 44: 8)
  Invitation to be the Foundation's monthly public policy speaker. Includes letters, receipt, schedule, and miscellany
- Americanism Educational League, California, 1998 September 8. (Folder 44: 9)
  Includes letters of invitation and appreciation, and printed matter
- Children's Educational Opportunity (CEO) Foundation National Conference on School Choice, Washington, D.C., 1998 September 23-24. (Folder 44: 10)
  Announcement, letter acknowledging acceptance of invitation to participate, and notes
- California Republican Party State Convention, Burbank, California, 1998 September 26. (Folder 44: 11)
  Invitation to participate and related materials
- W. W. Brady Foundation "Sex Is Better than Gender" meeting, Oak Brook, Illinois, 1998 October 7-9. (Folder 44: 12)
  Includes letters, program, and schedule
- Loyola University, Chicago, 1998 October 8. (Folder 44: 13)
  Receipt
- Boston College, Massachusetts, 1998 October 14. (Folder 44: 14)
  Itinerary and receipt
- Independent Women's Forum, 1998 October 15. (Folder 44: 15)
- Hudson Institute, Washington, D.C., 1998 October 16. (Folder 44: 16)
  Invitation and receipt
- Paul Revere Society, 1998 October 24. (Folder 44: 17)
- Washington Institute, 1998 October 28. (Folder 44: 18)
- Reason Foundation 1998 Gala Anniversary Banquet, 1998 November 12. (Folder 44: 19)
- "Redeeming the Wasteland," conference sponsored by the American Enterprise Institute and the Center for Media and Public Affairs, Inc., 1998 December 8. (Folder 44: 20)
  Letter, itinerary, and miscellany
- Originals conference, Washington, D.C., 1998 December 8-9 (Folder 44: 21)
- Jewish Policy Center Policy Forum, 1999 January 24. (Folder 44: 22)
- Bates College, Lewiston, Maine--Invitation to participate in the Muskie Archives series on public affairs, 1999 February 8. (Folder 44: 23)
- Republican Central Committee of Fresno County--Invitation to speak and related materials, 1999 February 12 (Folder 44: 24)
- California Republican Party convention, 1999 February 27. (Folder 44: 25)
  Receipts and itinerary
- The Escondido Republican Women Federated meeting, 1999 March 1. (Folder 44: 26)
  Includes itinerary of David Horowitz and financial records relating to his participation
- Heritage Foundation 25th anniversary, 1999 March 2. (Folder 44: 27)
  Invitation to a reception
- "Cultural Wars," Cardinal Mindszenty Foundation--Speech, 1999 March 20. (Folder 44: 28)
- Houston Community Publishing--Reception with David Horowitz, 1999 March 22. (Folder 44: 29)
  Itinerary and announcement
- Daughters of Liberty republican women, 1999 March 23. (Folder 44: 30)
- Rice University, Houston, Texas, 1999 March 23. (Folder 44: 31)
- Houston University, Texas, 1999 March 24. (Folder 44: 32)
- The Leadership Institute Summit, Arlington, Virginia, 1999 March 27-28. (Folder 44: 33)
  Invitation to David Horowitz to speak and materials related to the event
- Hawaii Pacific University--Speech by David Horowitz, 1999 May 3. (Folder 44: 34)
  Includes itinerary and financial records relating to his visit
- "Violence in Schools: What Happened at Columbine High?" Panel discussion, University of California, Los Angeles, California, 1999 May 19. (Folder 44: 35)
  Announcement of David Horowitz's participation and map
- The American Israel Public Affairs Committee (AIPAC) annual policy conference, Washington, D.C., 1999 May 23-25. (Folder 44: 36)
- Sioux Falls City Club, Sioux Falls, South Dakota, 1999 May 27. (Folder 44: 37)
  Receipts for speaking engagement
- Taxpayers conference, National Tax Payers Union Foundation, Washington, D.C., 1999 June 10. (Folder 44: 38)
  Invitation to speak, itinerary, receipts, and related materials
- University of Minnesota and the Freedom Club, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1999 September 13. (Folder 44: 39)
  Invoices and receipts
- Cyber Rendezvous conference, sponsored by the Hudson Institute, Jackson Hole, Wyoming, 1999 September 25-27. (Folder 44: 40)
  Letter of invitation, schedule, program, and biographical information on the speakers
- Republican National Committee 100 fall meeting, Washington, D.C., 1999 October 4-6. (Folder 44: 41)
  Program schedule and receipts
- Hillsdale College's Shavano Institute for National Leadership, Costa Mesa, California, 1999 October 12. (Folder 44: 42)
  Letter of appreciation for participation and related materials
- Association of American Physicians and Surgeons annual meeting, 1999 October 15. (Folder 44: 43)
  List of registrants, itinerary of David Horowitz, appreciation for his participation, and related materials
- The Lynde and Harry Bradley Foundation, Inc., David Horowitz luncheon, 1999 October 18. (Folder 44: 44)
  Itinerary of David Horowitz
- Institute of Politics, John F. Kennedy School of Government, Harvard University, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1999 October 20. (Folder 44: 45)
  David Horowitz was a guest in one of the sessions
- 14th Annual Bayliss Media Roast dinner, John Bayliss Broadcast Foundation, 1999 October 21. (Folder 44: 46)
  Announcement and letters
- Optimist Club of Pacific Palisades, 1999 October 26. (Folder 44: 47)
  Invitation to speak
- Mid-Atlantic Popular American/American Culture Association conference, Panthers, Pennsylvania, 1999 November 6. (Folder 44: 48)
  Announcement of participation of David Horowitz, panel listing, registration form, schedule, and miscellany
- Independent Women's Forum, 1999 November 8. (Folder 44: 49)
  David Horowitz was a speaker
- National Republican Senatorial Committee Inner Circle meeting, Marina Del Rey, 1997 July 17-19. (Box-folder 45: 1)
  Letter of appreciation for participation, program, and list of attendees
- National conservative student conference, Young America's Foundation, George Washington University, Washington, D.C., 1997 July 23. (Folder 45: 2)
  Itinerary and related materials
- Presidential Roundtable tenth anniversary summer forum, National Republican Senatorial Committee, Laguna Niguel, California, 1997 July 23-25. (Folder 45: 3)
- American Community Renewal Alliance event, Vista Del Mar, California, 1997 August 15. (Folder 45: 4)
  Program and RSVP list
- Originals conference, Seattle, Washington, 1997 September 3-4. (Folder 45: 5)
  Conference agenda, printed matter, and related materials
- Speech, Miami University, Oxford, Ohio, 1997 September 8. (Folder 45: 6)
  Itinerary, receipts, and schedule
- New York, 1997 September 24. (Folder 45: 7)
- Republican state convention, 1997 September 26-28. (Folder 45: 8)
- Claremont McKenna College, Claremont, California, 1997 October 1. (Folder 45: 9)
- San Ramon Republican Women conference, California, 1997 October 16. (Folder 45: 10)
  Itinerary, printed matter, and receipts
- Second Thoughts conference, 1997 October 17-18. (Folder 45: 11)
  Includes letters from David Horowitz to the participants
- Speech, Philanthropy Roundtable, Newport, Rhode Island, 1997 October 24. (Folder 45: 12)
  Includes agenda, letters, notes for remarks, receipts, and 1 compact sound cassette
- Texas--Fundraising letter, 1997 November. (Folder 45: 13)
  Includes itinerary and schedule
- Salem Communications Corporation--Speaking engagement at Salem's talk show conference, Dallas, Texas, 1997 November 3. (Folder 45: 14)
  Includes a thank you letter, itinerary, and schedule
- Speech, Young America's Foundation, University of Texas, Austin, Texas, 1997 November 5. (Folder 45: 15)
  Letters, clippings, and related materials
- Eagle Forum, Dallas, Texas, 1997 November 6. (Folder 45: 16)
  Brochure
- "Opportunities for Leadership," Chairman's Summit, Campaign America first annual policy briefing, Phoenix, Arizona, 1997 November 7. (Folder 45: 17)
  Invitation to participate in panel discussion, receipt, and miscellany
- Wisconsin Forum, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1997 November 11. (Folder 45: 18)